Investment and Distribution Buena Vista International Korea
A Toilet Pictures Production
I 'M YOUR DESTINY .
Stop it !
Please stop it !
Director - Byeong-ki Ahn
Ji-won Ha
Yu-mi Kim Woo-jae Choi
Ji-yeon Choi - Seo-woo Eun Jong-Soo Yi - Jeong-yun Choi
- Yes . - Where are you ?
- Are you OK ? - Why , what happened ?
Your articles on underage sex scandals caused hell here .
We 've had calls threatening you if you don 't stop writing them .
I 've had them too . We were ready for that .
Still , be careful .
For the next feature story ,
let 's try that paranormal stuff you talked about last year .
I told you this was the last article .
I 'm changing my mobile number and disappearing tomorrow .
Ji-won !
Hello ?
The scared look , so sexy .
Who is this ?
You can 't be that scared .
We 've only just begun .
Who are you ?
There 's no rush .
We 'll meet soon enough .
Hello .
Where are you off to so fast ? It won 't help to run .
You bastard !
Why don 't you say it to my face ?
Don 't give me that " deep voice " , rat .
Why aren 't you following me , rat ?
Is this Ji-won 's phone ?
Oh , Ho-jung .
So ? Do you know who it is ?
Some guys abused schoolgirls .
They were humiliated by my sex scandal articles .
It 's probably one of them .
The justice system will take care of them .
I 'll just go away and finish writing that novel .
What if he really comes after you ?
Have you decided where to go ?
No , I 'm still thinking .
But I can 't think of anywhere .
Then , go to Bangbae .
Our new house is empty .
I bought it about a year ago .
It 's too big .
We 'll move in when Young-ju grows up .
It 's well-furnished .
I think you will love it . What do you think ?
Thanks a lot . Is that OK ?
Do you think it 's OK to be alone there ?
It 's dangerous .
It 's not dangerous . I had a security system installed .
But I 'm still worried .
Hello , it 's clear .
NATIONAL PAINTING CONTEST
This is great .
I 'm sorry .
I should stay with you but Young-ju 's asleep .
Will you be OK ? Are you scared ?
I 'm not a little kid .
Don 't worry . I 'll be fine .
I 'm just worried .
Use my bedroom . It 's the most comfortable .
It 's so big . I 'm a little uneasy .
And it 's for you and your husband .
I 'll take the room upstairs .
The room at the end of the hall ? No , it 's full of junk .
I 'll clean it up .
You guys go and get some rest .
OK , I 'll lock up .
I 'll call you tomorrow .
He doesn 't quit .
Now what is it ?
Now what ?
That 's weird . This has never happened before .
- What ? - It only gives one number .
Hello ?
You drive well .
I 'm sorry .
Please try another branch .
I think it 's fate .
Just give me that number .
The girl in the picture is Modigliani 's daughter .
He painted it when his wife was pregnant .
He imagined her after observing the neighbours .
Thinking about their unborn daughter , they must have been happy .
I want Young-ju to grow up like that .
In a perfect family .
You have the perfect family .
You ought to paint again . You 're wasting your talent .
I can 't take care of the family and paint as well .
I 'm satisfied just enjoying the art of others .
Sorry about that .
Is it him again ?
No . I changed my number .
I shouldn 't get any more of those calls .
- What 's the number ? - 011-9998 ...
This is Renoir 's Irene Cahen d 'Anvers .
Young-ju !
Young-ju . Give us the phone .
Give us the phone !
Good girl .
Young-ju ! Give us the phone .
Give us the phone .
Young-ju !
Young-ju ! Young-ju !
It 's OK , Young-ju .
You 're worried , aren 't you ?
Whatever she heard on the phone must have scared her .
I don 't think it was the stalker , but it 's weird .
Anyway , call me if you go to the doctor tomorrow .
Sure .
Stop it . It hurts my ears .
Nothing 's wrong .
Is she OK ?
She 's just stressed from whatever scared her .
Give her some time . She 'll be fine .
Since you changed your number you 've had two calls .
Your friend Ho-jung and me .
That 's impossible .
I 've had three strange calls since then .
There are two possibilities .
The phone company 's records are messed up
or the stalker knows
how to block the calls from showing up .
Those sex scandal guys will be on trial in a few days .
It 's probably one of them .
But be careful .
Here 's a present .
You really think this is going to help ?
Zap them once and they 're out .
The men involved in the underage sex scandal have been identified .
It 's shocking that one of them , Dr Cha , is a psychiatrist .
A Miss Jung has testified that Dr Cha
repeatedly demanded perverted sex .
Hello .
Who the hell are you ?
Hello ? What 's that ?
Slow down now .
Tell what ?
You 're going to catch a cold .
Studying is hard , isn 't it ?
That 's rose .
I love that faint flower fragrance .
Now , which way ?
I love you more than anything .
If you hurt , then I hurt too .
So don 't be hurting any more , OK ?
You 're such a strong woman .
I thought you 'd give up
when the doctor said you couldn 't get pregnant .
But with artificial insemination , you did it .
I was really worried .
You get through everything .
Do you know how nervous I get
watching you go from crisis to crisis ?
I couldn 't have done it without you .
- Young-ju ! - Daddy , I 'm scared .
Ji-won ! What do you think she heard ?
I was so scared .
It started after
she answered my phone in the gallery , didn 't it ?
I checked the phone records , but there 's nothing there .
Ji-won .
How about changing your number again ?
Then he can 't call .
Hello ?
Hey , Chang-hoon ! How are you ?
Yeah , just a minute .
It 's Chang-hoon .
Hi , honey .
You 're getting big .
Young-ju .
Do you remember what you heard on my phone ?
No .
Aunt ! Do you know what love is ?
Love ?
Do you know love ?
No , you wouldn 't know what real love is .
You 're in love with somebody .
Who is it ?
Daddy .
So , you said you love your daddy .
What about your mummy ?
Do you love her ?
You 're tired .
Go to sleep .
- Aunt ! - Yes ?
If that woman calls again , tell her not to yell .
It scares me .
You don 't look good . Is it the phone calls ?
Did you find anything ?
There is no record of a call at that time .
Even the department at the phone company tracking the calls
has no idea .
Are we at a dead end ?
I 've found this .
People who have had that number .
Nothing strange in their background .
But both people who had that number died .
One in a car crash , the other a heart attack .
It 's not necessarily murder , but it is strange .
Finish eating and let 's make Daddy a card .
I 've got everything ready .
A Christmas card ?
Yes .
Who is it ?
Flower delivery .
What is it ?
Daddy sent them .
Eat !
I said eat ! Eat !
Young-ju , what 's the matter ?
Nothing .
Young-ju ?
What 's wrong with you ?
He worked hard driving his taxi .
He talked about his dream of opening a restaurant .
Then his wife bought that mobile phone .
Maybe the phone killed him .
The mobile phone ?
After he got the phone , he started getting weird calls .
Nobody talked .
Just a bone-chilling sound !
It was like his soul was gone .
He said he wouldn 't do night duty .
I asked him why , and he said something about a ghost .
What caused the crash ?
Here it is .
Bangbae ?
Ho-jung !
What 's going on ?
She has a strong desire to be with her father .
The long hair represents her
as an adult thinking sexually of her father .
She gets jealous , when you and your husband get intimate .
She doesn 't want to leave her dad .
Is she trying to push me away ?
At her age , it 's just a temporary thing .
You mean there 's nothing else wrong with her ?
No .
She 's healthy and intelligent .
You have a very intelligent little girl .
Let 's do it again .
Wouldn 't it be great if I were on TV ,
if I were on TV ?
Anyway , she lived alone .
For some reason she came home after midnight every night .
Before she died , you should have seen her face .
You know , it was ghostly white .
Was it suicide ?
Who commits suicide in a lift ?
They said it was a heart attack caused by a fit .
She asked me to call when the trial date was set .
Is she asleep ?
What 's this ?
Hey ? Are you OK ?
" One winter day , a queen was sewing by the window .
" Then the queen pricked her finger with her needle .
" Three drops of blood fell into the snow .
" The red on the white looked so beautiful .
" ' Lf only I had a child as white as snow , as red as blood
" and as black as this frame . '
" ... And the prince and Snow White lived happily ever after . "
Yeah , right ! Shit !
We grow up with this crap .
That 's why
we have little stupid princesses around .
What a stupid story !
Detective ?
Get back , he needs surgery .
You made a gross mistake .
You started all this .
You 're crazy .
How does it feel to be hanging there ?
Beg for your life .
What 's the matter ?
Why 's the fridge open ?
You 're going to get sick .
Stop worrying .
The doctor said she 's fine .
Let 's wait a while .
- If she gets worse we can admit her . - I don 't want her admitted .
I 'm sorry .
My little princess is awake .
Give me a kiss .
Young-ju !
Young-ju ?
What are you doing ?
- Young-ju ? - Young-ju . What 's wrong ?
Hi !
You 're good on the piano .
You play Moonlight Sonata .
Moonlight Sonata ?
You play it every night .
My mum doesn 't let me play at night .
My mum says the music comes from your house .
Anybody home ?
She had two mobile numbers ?
I didn 't know it until she was gone .
There was only one phone .
Her number was 9726-6644 .
When we couldn 't find her , I cancelled the 9998-6644 number .
I kept her number to keep hope alive .
There were a lot of rumours when Jin-hee disappeared .
She ran away with a boyfriend .
She became the most famous prostitute in downtown .
Then they said she got killed
and came back to haunt the school .
Why do you say that ?
We heard piano music in an empty concert hall at night .
A teacher went in but nobody was there .
We could hear the piano off and on .
The Moonlight Sonata ?
How did you know that ?
She was practising that song before she disappeared .
Some weird stuff happened to Sang-mi afterwards .
She passed out on the bathroom floor with a mobile phone next to her .
Everybody said it was Jin-hee calling from the dead .
Now everybody 's scared of mobile phones .
All phones on your desks .
That does it .
Sang-mi . Get up here .
Stop it ! Stop it !
Jin-hee was the first to have my phone number .
And she gave it to somebody .
I 'm sure it was a man .
What proof do you have ?
I couldn 't understand everything over the phone .
But she was mad at some guy .
When she disappeared , her mum cancelled the number .
The next two people who got that number died strange deaths .
I 'm sure that guy has something to do with her disappearance
or maybe he ...
Are you saying she was murdered ?
And her spirit is in Young-ju ?
Does that make sense to you ?
But Jin-hee ...
Ji-won , you 're not helping out by saying this crap .
Honey !
Sorry .
Your mother said she found a good child psychologist .
Let 's get Young-ju some treatment
and she 'll be fine .
Ji-won , enough of this phone
and Jin-hee , OK ?
But Young-ju could be in trouble .
We should find out why .
The doctor will find out .
Stay out of our business .
I 'll pretend I didn 't hear you tonight .
Hold still . I 'm trying .
Look how tiny she is .
Thank you .
If it wasn 't for you , we wouldn 't have Young-ju .
If you hadn 't provided the eggs .
Forget about it .
We weren 't going to tell anyone .
When I asked you ,
I was worried you 'd refuse .
I think of her as my own .
Just raise her to be as beautiful as you , deal ?
Let 's do it .
The voice you heard on the phone was Jin-hee 's .
The voice of sad and vengeful Jin-hee !
You 're right . Your number was hers .
She was excited she had two phones with the same last digits .
She was going to give one to somebody she loved .
She looked
really happy .
If you asked who he was , she 'd say it was a secret .
She 'd disappear after school .
She wanted to hang out with me so she could brag about him .
I don 't know who he was , but
she liked him a lot .
He liked the Moonlight Sonata ,
so she asked me to teach her .
She wasn 't good , but she practised very hard .
What 's wrong with me ?
You have no feeling .
He won 't fall in love with that .
Here , watch me .
Try it .
One day he started avoiding her calls .
Let 's go in .
- Come on , let 's go . - You go in .
You 're going to be late .
I said , you go in .
LOVE YOU . PLEASE ANSWER ...
Does that make love last ?
Of course , just like that .
Tell us more .
Take the letters in your name ,
and add them to the guy 's name .
See , it 's 10 . Then , send him this message .
" I 'm your destiny . "
At 10 minutes past the hour .
But if I send it , he 'll know my number .
I 'm not through .
You punch in his number , not yours .
I 'll have to try it .
By the way , who 's this guy ?
Leonardo DiCaprio .
Really ?
How did you get his phone number ?
Hey , would you shut up ? I can 't sleep .
What 's the matter with her ?
You got dumped . So , now you 're writing ?
Forget what you saw .
Or I 'll kill you .
I don 't know how to get away from her .
But if you don 't want to end up dead
there 's only one solution .
Don 't answer the phone .
Don 't look at the phone .
You didn 't come alone ?
Jin-hee .
Jin-hee came with you ?
LOVE
You 're going to catch a cold .
I like this . I suppose it 's not your style .
Actually
it 's good .
The last digits are the same .
Nobody else can answer it .
I 'm the only one that can call it .
I 'm sorry .
Don 't carry this handkerchief .
How could you bring it ?
I 'm sorry , I forgot .
You forgot ?
You take care of everything she gives you .
Did you forget your promise to me ?
What 's so great about this ?
What ?
Does that upset you ?
Jin-hee .
We probably shouldn 't meet .
For a while .
Is that up to you ?
She came back from my in-laws .
You 're making it worse .
I 'm sorry .
You can keep the handkerchief .
I can wait for a few days .
Just don 't say I can 't see you .
I love you .
I couldn 't live without you .
The phone is off . Do you want to leave a message ?
The call will be charged .
He wavered for a moment .
But this will pass .
I believe in our love .
A HAPPY FAMILY LEADS TO SUCCESS
CEO OF DAEHAN BONDS CHANG-HOON LEE
What happened to Jin-hee ?
If you don 't come clean , what will happen to Young-ju ?
There 's no time .
If you don 't tell , I 'm going to .
It will save Young-ju .
- Hi , Ho-jung . - Young-ju 's gone .
What should I do ?
What do you mean , she 's gone ?
I gave her some medicine and put her to bed .
I fell asleep too . When I woke up , she was gone .
Who is this ?
That 's enough .
What exactly do you want ?
Chang-hoon 's the one who did you wrong .
Leave Young-ju alone .
What do you gain from this ?
He wavered for a moment . But this will pass .
I believe in our love .
Where is Young-ju ?
Young-ju ! Be careful ! I 'm coming , just stay there .
" Young-ju , Young-ju . "
I 'm sick of that .
Which one of you would like to die for me ?
Well , speak up .
Jin-hee !
It 's Daddy .
Where ?
That 's Daddy , isn 't it ?
Isn 't that Daddy ?
That 's not him .
He 's at the office now .
I 'M WAITING AT THE PARK NOW .
- First message . - No night school tonight .
Let 's meet .
Why are you avoiding me ?
I 'm going to tell everything .
Don 't you want to see me ?
I really want to see you .
I am coming to your office tomorrow .
I 'm four weeks along .
I 'm pregnant .
What 's up ?
I was in the area .
You 're busy . I 'm bothering you .
So , you 're going to remodel the Bangbae house by yourself ?
It 's hard work .
We 're not moving yet . There 's no hurry .
OK ! I need to go to Japan on business tomorrow .
It 'll take three days .
I know you haven 't been back long . I 'm so sorry .
Are you ?
That 's OK .
The phone is off . Please leave a message ...
At your age , you could fall for a kind , older man .
But he 's not as simple as you .
Men and girls are different .
Don 't mistake me for a child .
You 'll find somebody better than him .
I don 't need anybody else .
He 'll come back to his family .
You hope .
Let 's get real . Abort the baby .
How can you be responsible for a baby when you 're in school ?
Nobody will take care of that baby .
I 'm not asking you to .
I 'm having the baby .
My lover and I made this baby .
You wouldn 't understand , because you borrowed an egg .
You share nothing with him .
You 're in a fantasy land .
If he really loved you , why won 't he take your calls ?
Don 't you get it ?
No , he loves me .
Do you want me to tell you how much we 've loved ?
We made love here every day while you were gone .
He said he 'd never been happier .
You only look good on the outside .
Do you know how much you smother him ?
You think you can create love .
He 's really sick of you .
I 'm not like you .
His love , his baby . I can take everything .
That 's enough !
Please leave him .
Then I 'll give you anything you want .
Anything I want ?
Divorce him .
Do you think he loves you ?
Get real !
You 're the one in a fantasy land .
He loves me !
You want proof ?
You 're dead !
Ji-won , do you remember ?
When I found out I was sterile
I just wanted to die .
When I saw children on the street
I wanted to run away with one .
When I saw a pregnant woman
I would cry .
When I 'd open my eyes in the morning
the world would be
like shattered glass .
It was you that gave me strength .
But do you know
how jealous I get when you look into Young-ju 's eyes ?
Maybe
she would see you as her mother .
She 's mine .
I carried her for 10 months . I suffered having her .
I would do anything for her to be happy .
Yes , I can do everything .
I can .
You don 't understand .
Jin-hee didn 't deserve to die .
She became a vengeful ghost .
Let 's say you cover everything up .
What about Young-ju ?
You think Young-ju will be happy ?
Like before ?
Shut up !
She 's mine and I 'll raise her .
She 'll never know
if you just keep your mouth shut .
Stop it .
Look at her .
Don 't you understand ?
It 's not just Young-ju .
You 're in danger too .
When he found out Jin-hee was dead ,
he killed you .
Then he felt bad about it and killed himself .